contactatonce.com 2018-05-05

# Privacy Policy & Data Security | Contact at Once!

**Privacy Policy**

Effective Date:  March 2, 2018 

Contact At Once! values your privacy.   This privacy policy explains what personal data we collect from you and how we use it.   This privacy policy applies if you visit Contact At Once!'s corporate websites or social media or other web pages located on third-party websites, use any mobile application(s) provided by Contact At Once! or register to attend any of Contact At Once!’s corporate events.  This privacy policy also applies if you use Contact At Once!’s websites, hosted services, products, applications and/or content (collectively, the "Services") directly or through a Contact At Once! customer (for example, on a Contact At Once! customer's website or mobile application). 

What does Contact At Once! do?

What information do we collect from you?

How does Contact At Once! collect information from you?

How does Contact At Once! use the information it collects about me?

Does Contact At Once! use cookies?

Sharing of information collected 

Access and changes to personal data

Third-party integrations

How can I review, correct, delete, or receive a copy of my information with Contact At Once! or withdraw my consent from Contact At Once! processing my personal data? 

How does Contact At Once! keep my information secure?

Additional mobile considerations

Contact At Once! forums and blogs

International data transfers

Canadian residents

Miscellaneous

Contact At Once! provides mobile and online messaging technologies that enable digital communication between our business customers and consumers through chat, voice, messaging and other methods. 

If you engage with a brand that uses our Services, we may collect: 

·         Chat and messaging transcripts on behalf of the brand,

·         Information on behalf of and/or requested by the brand, such as information related to your browsing, purchasing and online behavior and activities, and 

·         Automatic information, such as IP address, operating system, geographic location information and type of device used. 

If you visit our websites or use our apps, we may also collect: 

·         Information you provide to us, including:

o    Personal information, such as your name and contact information, 

o    Surveys, transcripts and recordings of your communications with us, 

o    Information you provide on our forums and blogs

·         Automatic information, such as: 

o    Web browser and usage information, including IP address, browser types, page view tallies, time spent on each page, page browsing information, operating system, geographic location information and type of device used. 

We collect information when you engage with a brand that uses our Services, which may be enabled on the brand’s website or in its mobile applications, voice or SMS messaging capabilities, social media page/profile or other digital engagement solutions. 

In addition, we may collect information through the following methods if you visit our websites or use our apps: 

o    Your communications with Contact At Once !,

o    Your requests for information, news and other content,

o    Your participation in one or more Contact At Once! forums or blogs,

o    A technical support request you submit, 

o    Your participation in a Contact At Once! promotion, or 

o    Recruitment and job applications. 

We may also collect information from our direct interactions with you (such as through your attendance at a trade show or through sales inquiries), publicly available data or data provided by third-party sources, such as marketing opt-in lists.

We use the information we collect to provide and improve our services. 

If you engage with a brand that uses our Services, we use the information we collect on behalf of and as directed by the brand.  For example, we may use your information to determine whether to deploy a chat button to allow the brand to engage with you or to deploy content, such as a banner offering a coupon, on your browser. 

If you visit our websites or use our apps, we may also use your information for the following purposes: 

o    To deliver information requested by you, for example in response to technical support requests, 

o    To deliver marketing or other materials to you, 

o    For promotions you may enter into, or 

o    If you submit a resume or CV, to considering you for employment with Contact At Once !.

Contact At Once! may retain your information for a period of time consistent with the original purpose of collection. For example, if you engage with a brand that uses our Services, we may retain your information for the period of time agreed on with the brand. We may also retain your information during the period of time needed for Contact At Once! to pursue our legitimate business interests, conduct audits, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. 

We may use cookies and other identification technologies for record keeping purposes and to enhance your experience, if you choose to visit our websites  

**Cookies:**  
Cookies are small text files stored on a visitor’s web browser and applications. Cookies are often used to make web-browsing easier by performing functions such as saving passwords and maintaining lists of personal preferences regarding the use of the website. 

Our websites, apps and Services may use the following types of cookies: 

·      Strictly Necessary Cookies – these cookies are essential to enable you to browse our websites, apps and Services and use the available features. 

·      Performance Cookies – these cookies collect information about how you use our websites, apps and Services. For instance, these cookies track which pages you visit most. This data may be used to help optimize our websites, apps and Services and make it easier for you to navigate within them. These cookies do not collect information that identifies you; all information is aggregated and anonymous. 

·      Functionality Cookies – these cookies allow our websites, apps and Services to remember choices you make while browsing, such as geographic location and preferences such as text size and fonts. The information collected by these cookies will not personally identify you. 

**Other identification technologies that may be used by Contact At Once! websites, apps and Services:**

·         Pixel tags (also called beacons or pixels) – these are small blocks of code installed on (or called by) a webpage or application, which can retrieve certain information about your device and browser, including device type, operating system, browser type and version, website visited, time of visit, referring website, IP address and other similar information. ****

·         Software Development Kits (also called SDKs) - function like pixels and cookies, but operate in the mobile application context where pixels and cookies cannot always function. The application developer can install pieces of code (the SDK) into the application to collect certain information about user interaction with the application and information about the user device and network information. 

**Third-party technologies:**

Contact At Once! may use third-party service providers who are authorized to place cookies, pixel tags or similar technologies on our websites, apps and Services with our permission.   These technologies help us compile metrics and analytics (without collecting personally identifiable information) to help improve our websites, apps and Services.    Third-party cookies and technologies are covered by the third party’s privacy policy. 

**Your choice:**

Web browsers are usually set to accept cookies. However, if you prefer not to receive cookies, you typically have the option of setting your browser to refuse cookies. If your browser is set to refuse cookies, it is likely that some of the functionality offered by Contact  At Once! will not be available or will not work as effectively for you. 

For further information about cookies, including how to see what cookies have been set on your device and how to manage and delete them, you can visit [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/) and [www.youronlinechoices.eu](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/). 

**Do Not Track**

Various browsers, including Internet Explorer, Firefox and Safari, currently offer a "do not track" or "DNT" option that relies on a technology that sends a signal to websites a user visits about that user’s browser DNT preferences. While Contact At Once! attempts to honor the DNT instructions received from a user’s browser, Contact At Once! cannot guarantee that it will always respond to such signals because a common industry standard for DNT has not been adopted. Contact At Once! will continue to monitor developments around DNT browser technology. 

Contact At Once! does not sell, trade or rent personal information provided by you in any transcript, survey or recording for direct marketing or any other purpose, except as provided in this privacy policy or with your permission.  Contact At Once! does not disclose the contents of transcripts, surveys or recordings other than to service providers performing services on behalf of Contact At Once!, other than as provided in this privacy policy or with your permission.

_Brand you have engaged with through the Services_

If you engage with a brand that uses our Services, we may also share your information with that brand. 

_For legal reasons_

We may share your information if we reasonably believe that it:  (i) is necessary to comply with a legal process (such as a court order, subpoena, or search warrant) or other legal requirement of any governmental authority; (ii) would potentially mitigate our liability in an actual or potential lawsuit; (iii) is necessary to enforce this privacy policy or our Terms of Use athttp://www.contactatonce.com/terms-of-use/ or any other agreement in place between you and Contact At Once!; (iv) is necessary to investigate and prevent unauthorized transactions or other illegal activities; and/or (v) is otherwise necessary or appropriate to protect our rights or property or the rights or property of any person or entity. 

_To deliver and improve the Services_

We may aggregate information so that it is not personally identifiable and use and share such aggregated information for training and quality assurance purposes and to deliver and improve our Services. 

_Service providers_

We use a limited number of third-party service providers to assist us in making our websites and Services available to visitors and users. For example, we may share data with third parties who provide services to us, such as credit card processing services, analytics and data storage services. These third parties may access, process or store personal data in the course of providing their services. 

_Business partners_

From time to time, we may partner with other companies to allow [Contact At Once!](http://www.contactatonce.com/) and its customers to offer integrations with our Services. If you engage with a brand that uses one of these integrations, [Contact At Once!](http://www.contactatonce.com/) may share your data with the third-party partner, receive data about you from the third-party partner, and/or combine third-party partner data about you with information about you that we collect. We do not control how a third-party partner may use your data. Use of your information by the third-party partner there is governed by its privacy policies. If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this way, you may opt not to use such integrations. 

_Affiliates_

We may share your information with subsidiaries, parent companies, or other affiliates of the Contact At Once! corporate group in order to deliver and improve the Services. 

_Other third parties_

The Cookies section above addresses the information Contact At Once! or third parties collect through cookies, pixel tags, SDKs, and similar third-party technologies and how you can control cookies through your web browsers. Contact At Once! may also disclose your personal information to any third party with your prior consent. 

If you elect to engage in any communication or engagement session with Contact At Once! or a customer that uses our Services, it is up to you to decide what, if any, information to provide during such session.   Depending on your request, it may not be possible for us or our customer to address all of your questions without further information from you.  Nevertheless, if you do not wish to provide certain information, then you should not do so.   

From time to time, we may partner with other companies to allow Contact At Once! and its customers to offer integrations with our Services.  If you engage with a brand that uses one of these integrations, Contact At Once! may share your data with the third-party partner, receive data about you from the third-party partner, and/or combine third-party partner data about you with information about you that we collect.  We do not control how a third-party partner may use your data.    Use of your information by the third-party partner there is governed by its privacy policies.  If you do not wish for your information to be shared in this way, you may opt not to use such integrations.

If you have opted-in to receive Contact At Once Once!’s marketing or advertising communications, you may, at any time, opt out of receiving further communications by clicking on the opt-out link at the bottom of a marketing or advertising email you receive.   You may also contact us at [privacy@contactatonce.com](mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com) to opt out or to request changes to your personal information.

You may request to review, correct, delete, or receive a copy of any of the personal information you’ve provided to a Brand that uses the Services or withdraw your consent to Contact At Once! processing your personal data by either contacting the brand directly or by contacting us at [privacy@contactatonce.com](mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com), and we will respond within a reasonable period of time and can help coordinate with and support the brand as needed to respond to your request.  

We use security measures designed to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.    For certain Contact At Once! Services, chat/messaging transcripts are encrypted during transmission.   In addition, transcripts that we store are maintained and archived on secure, hardened servers that are hosted on highly secure data centers.     Access to this data is protected by multiple layers of controls, including firewalls, role-based access controls, authentication mechanisms and monitoring.     Data is backed up, and archives are stored off-site in a secure location. 

If you are communicating with a brand that uses our Services, you should review the privacy practices of that brand to understand which security measures they use.  

In addition to the other terms in this policy, if you use our mobile application(s), access our mobile-optimized websites or have a conversation with a Contact At Once! customer that uses our Services in its mobile application(s), we may receive information about your location and your mobile device, including a unique identifier for your device.     Most mobile phones allow you to control or disable location services in the device’s settings menu.     If you have questions about how to turn off location services, please contact your mobile phone manufacturer or mobile service carrier.     You may also choose to allow our mobile application(s) to access features available on your device, such as the device’s camera and microphone, or to access the data stored on your device, such as photos and videos, to share such media while using the application(s). 

If you have opted-in to receive SMS messages from Contact At Once!, you may opt out by following the opt-out instructions that we provide or by contacting us at  [privacy@contactatonce.com](mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com). 

If you have opted-in to receive SMS messages from one of our customers, you may opt out by following the opt-out instructions provided by the brand you are communicating with or by contacting the brand.   You may also contact us at [privacy@contactatonce.com](mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com), and we can help put you in touch with the brand regarding your request. 

Information that you share on Contact At Once! forums or blogs becomes publicly available and therefore may be read, collected, copied and used by other users for any purposes at their discretion.   Because this information is publicly available, Contact At  Once!’s privacy obligations outlined in this privacy policy do not apply to your use of any such forums or blogs.

If you are located outside of the United States, please note that we may transfer your personal data outside your country of origin.   By providing or making available your personal data, you consent to that transfer. Based on applicable laws in your country of residence, you may have certain rights with respect to your personal data that we retain. 

We will take steps to ensure that your data is subject to appropriate safeguards required under this privacy policy, applicable data protection laws, and appropriate legally recognized data transfer adequacy mechanisms which may include entering into European Commission-approved standard contractual clauses related to transfers of personal information (available at <http://ec.europa.eu/justice/dataprotection/internationaltransfers/transfer/index_en.html>) or a valid Privacy Shield certification in the case of a transfer to a Privacy Shield-certified US recipient (certifications may be viewed at <https://www.privacyshield.gov/welcome>). For residents of the European Economic Area and Switzerland, Contact At Once! will executed standard contractual clauses among Contact At Once! affiliates for the purpose of its lawful transfers of personal data to the United States. 

We adhere to the principles of the EU-US Privacy Shield Framework regarding the collection, use and retention of personal information transferred from the European Union to the United States and have certified our compliance with the U.S. Department of Commerce.    To learn more about the Privacy Shield Framework and to view our certification, visit the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield website at  [www.privacyshield.gov](file:///power/users$/etroshina/WEBSITE/Privacy%20Policy/www.privacyshield.gov).

We use a limited number of third-party service providers to assist us in making our websites and Services available to visitors and users.   For example, we may share data with third parties who provide services to us, such as credit card processing services, analytics and data storage services.   These third parties may access, process or store personal data in the course of providing their services.     We currently maintain contracts with these third parties restricting their access, use and disclosure of personal data.   Contact At Once! is responsible if these third parties process personal data in violation of the Privacy Shield principles (unless Contact At Once! can prove that it’s not responsible for the third party’s action that violated the Privacy Shield principles). 

With respect to personal data received or transferred pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, we are subject to the regulatory enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.     In certain situations, we may be required to disclose personal data in response to lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or law enforcement requirements. 

EU individuals have the right to access personal data about them, and to limit use and disclosure of their personal data.   With our Privacy Shield certification, Contact At Once! has committed to respect those rights.   Because our personnel has limited ability to access personal data our customers submit through our Services, if you wish to request access to or to limit use and/or disclosure of your personal data, please contact us with the name of the Contact At Once! customer through which you used our Services.   We will refer your request to that customer, and will support them as needed in responding to your request. 

Any inquiries or complaints regarding our data privacy practices or Privacy Shield compliance may be directed to privacy@contactatonce.com.    We will respond within 30 days and provide appropriate recourse at no cost to you.     If we fail to respond within that time, or if our response does not address your concern, you may contact JAMS at  [www.jamsadr.com](https://www.jamsadr.com/), an independent third-party dispute resolution mechanism based in the United States.     If neither Contact At Once! nor JAMS resolves your complaint, the Privacy Shield Panel, a binding arbitration mechanism provided under the Privacy Shield program, may be available to you. 

Contact At Once! continues to comply with the underlying principles of the US-Swiss Safe Harbor framework as set forth by the US Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal data from Switzerland.   Contact At Once! has certified, under its parent company LivePerson, Inc., that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement.   To learn more about the Safe Harbor program and to view the parent company LivePerson, Inc’s certification, please visit[www.export.gov/safeharbor/](http://www.export.gov/safeharbor/).  If you have an unresolved privacy or data use concern, please contact us at  [privacy@contactatonce.com](mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com). 

Canadian individuals are entitled to submit a request to consult and access their personal information held by us. They can also request the rectification of their personal information if it is inaccurate, incomplete or ambiguous, or if the collection, disclosure or retention thereof is not authorized by law.  

If you have any questions concerning this Policy, or about the collection, use or disclosure of your personal information, or if you wish to make a request for access to, or to rectify, your personal information, please contact to us at [privacy@contactatonce.com](mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com)  

We will respond to any request for access or rectification within 30 days of the date your written request is received. In the event of a refusal to provide or correct the information, we will inform you of the grounds for our refusal, subject to any restrictions provided by law, and inform you of your recourses.  

The Services are not directed to individuals under 18. If you are under the age of 18, you may not use the Services or provide any personal information to us. Contact At Once! does not knowingly collect personal information from individuals under the age of 18. If you are a parent of an individual under 18 and believe your child has provided personal information to Contact At Once!, or if you are a California resident under the age of 18 and wish to remove content you have made publicly available, please contact us at <a href="mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com%3Eprivacy@contactatonce.com%3C/a%3E" ,="" where="" you="" may="" request="" to="" exercise="" your="" applicable="" access,="" rectification,="" cancellation,="" and="" or="" objection="" rights.="" contact="" at="" once!reserves="" the="" right="" immediately="" delete="" information="" of="" any="" individual,="" extent="" permitted="" by="" law,="" who="" it="" believes="" is="" under="" age="" 18.="" <span="">  <a href="mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com%3Eprivacy@contactatonce.com%3C/a%3E" ,="" where="" you="" may="" request="" to="" exercise="" your="" applicable="" access,="" rectification,="" cancellation,="" and="" or="" objection="" rights.="" contact="" at="" once!reserves="" the="" right="" immediately="" delete="" information="" of="" any="" individual,="" extent="" permitted="" by="" law,="" who="" it="" believes="" is="" under="" age="" 18.="" <span="">

We recommend that you review this privacy policy periodically, as we may update it from time to time.  Your use of our websites, apps and Services, as applicable, constitutes your consent to the new privacy policy to the fullest extent permitted by law. 

We recommend that you review this privacy policy periodically, as we may update it from time to time.    We encourage Your use of our websites, apps and Services, as applicable, constitutes your consent to the new privacy policy to the fullest extent permitted by law.  

We are not responsible for and do not control the privacy practices of any of our customers or any other third party.  We encourage you to review the privacy practices of each third party.  We welcome your feedback on our privacy policy.  Please send any comments or questions to  [privacy@contactatonce.com](mailto:privacy@contactatonce.com) or to Contact at Once! LLC, Attn: Legal Department – Privacy, 475 Tenth Ave., 5th Floor, New York, NY 10018.
